<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Eat, sleep, code, repeat</title>
    <link>https://anthony.truskinger.name/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Eat, sleep, code, repeat</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 22:24:53 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anthony.truskinger.name/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Building a Blog With Hugo (Eventually)</title>
      <link>https://anthony.truskinger.name/posts/building-blog-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 22:24:53 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthony.truskinger.name/posts/building-blog-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>I have tried many times to start a blog. I think it&amp;rsquo;s important for me to write often because writing is something I have difficulty concentrating on. Some might find my distaste and associated boredom with writing ironic given I elected to do a PhD&amp;hellip; but I digress.
Required features These are the requirement I have always wanted for a blog platform:
 Free hosting Complete customisation Complete transparency&amp;ndash;As a professional point of pride, I need to understand how it all works Minimal overhead&amp;ndash;I don&amp;rsquo;t want to be patching (even more) servers  Putting those requirements together, I decided I wanted to use a static website generator.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Excessive Memory Usage in Redis</title>
      <link>https://anthony.truskinger.name/posts/investigating-excessive-memory-usage-in-redis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Sep 2016 18:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthony.truskinger.name/posts/investigating-excessive-memory-usage-in-redis/</guid>
      <description>At www.ecosounds.org we use Resque as our asynchronous job processing system. Resque was created, used, and open sourced by GitHub. It is a queue based implementation built on top of Redis. Redis is an in memory, key-value store (a database) that is exceptionally fast.
The system has its limitations but has generally worked pretty well for us. We’ve run in excess of a million jobs through Resque and we consider that to be a decent amount for a small site like ours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching Vagrant to Hyper-V</title>
      <link>https://anthony.truskinger.name/posts/switching-vagrant-to-hyperv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anthony.truskinger.name/posts/switching-vagrant-to-hyperv/</guid>
      <description>I use Vagrant to script and automate virtual machines used for development purposes. When I first started using Vagrant I didn&amp;rsquo;t really understand its utility or its place in the development cycle. Now though I&amp;rsquo;m quite happy in my understanding that it is just a automation layer, a scripting abstraction, used to paste over the differences of different virtualization layers&amp;ndash;most of the time at least.
There are of course other alternative to using virtual machines for development environments.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>